chinaccelerator.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Statement - Chinaccelerator 中国加速

* **General**

We may collect your personal data from direct and indirect interactions with you to provide our services as agreed by you or to fulfill our contractual obligations with you.

In this regard we may gather personal data that may include your:  
Name, address, nationality, email address, telephone number, bank account details, job title, name of employer, bank account details, tax ID or your national insurance number, forms of identification.

We may use this information to:  
Set up meetings with you, maintain a record of your contacts, respond to your enquiries and fulfill your requests, assist you with your transactions or provide you with investor related services.

The use and processing of your personal data is necessary for our legitimate interests in providing our services, carrying out of administrative duties, the running of our business and in order to make or advise on investment decisions.

* **Communications And Correspondence**

In the course of communications or correspondence with you we may need to collect your personal data in order to develop our services and offerings and inform our marketing strategy.

In this regard we may gather the following personal data:  
Name, residential or business address, job title, name of employer, nationality, email address, home or office address.

The use and processing of your personal data is required for our legitimate interests to develop our services, grow our business and inform our marketing strategy.

* **Existing And Potential Limited Partners**

Limited Partners (“LPs”) include any individual who invests in any fund managed by SOSV or its affiliates and/or individuals who invest or may potentially invest in our portfolio companies.

We may collect your personal data for the following purposes:  
Due diligence including identity verification and eligibility checks, to maintain communications by storing a record of contacts, organising meetings with you, responding to your enquiries and requests, investment management i.e capital calls, payments and cash distributions, the completion of fund related documentation.

In this regard we may gather the following personal data:  
Name, residential address, tax ID, social security number, forms of identification, email addresses, telephone numbers, bank account details.

We use and process this information for the following purposes and legitimate interests:  
providing our services, administrative purposes, making or advising on investment decisions, performance of contractual relationships, to comply with relevant regulations and laws, tax and compliance obligations including anti money laundering regulations and criminal background checks.

* **Co-Investors Or Potential Co-Investors**

Co-Investors or potential co-investors include individuals who solely or as part of a corporation invest in the same portfolio companies as SOSV.

In this regard we may gather the following personal data:  
Name, residential address, telephone number, social security number, forms of identification, email addresses, telephone numbers, job title, employer details.

We use and process this information for the following purposes and legitimate interests:  
providing our services, administrative purposes, making or advising on investment decisions, performance of contractual relationships, to comply with relevant regulations, laws, tax and compliance obligations.

* **Corporate Partners And Mentors**

Corporate partners or mentors include any individual who work with SOSV to provide guidance and support to our Portfolio Companies on the basis of their expertise and skill in a given area.

We may collect personal data from corporate partners and mentors including:  
Name, email address, telephone number, job title, bank account details, area of business and employment history.

We use and process such personal data for our legitimate interests such as providing services, running our business and administrative purposes.

* **Portfolio Companies**

We gather personal data from individuals involved in our portfolio companies for the following purposes:  
Founder, director, shareholder and relevant third party identity verification, due diligence checks, ongoing investment management, analysis of company proposals, pitches and presentations, organising meetings with you and maintaining a record of contacts.

Personal data collected for the above purposes include:  
Founder, director and shareholder names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, bank account details; founder nationalities and gender.

We use and process such personal data for the following purposes and legitimate interests - Providing program and general services; administrative purposes; making or advising on investment decisions; performance of contract rights and obligations with you.

* **Employees And Applicant Employees Or Interns**

Our employee’s personal data is held on various internal systems. An employee’s personal data policy has been made available to all our employee’s setting out their rights as a data subject. Our legal basis for such processing concerns the employer/ employee contractual relationship.

We collect personal data of applicant employees in order to consider and manage employment applications.

Personal data collected may include the following:  
Name, address, date of birth, social security number or tax ID, form of identification, nationality, email address, telephone number, job title, employment history and resumé.

We require the above information in accordance with your consent and for our legitimate interests in providing our services, running our business, administrative purposes, to enable performance of contractual relations, allow us to progress your potential employment or internship.
